{
    "id": "5731ac1510754f02b286ee711c0e45c5",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "English ................................ all over the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "speaks",
                "is spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c686b02ba8414ad8a5e621a90be0fbed"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief .................................. by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has arrested",
                "has been arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c710ca4d92594ebab7e853f66c590426"
        },
        {
            "question": "The show ....................................... by both men and women.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is watching",
                "is being watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "40132d11009246239995da9ef65ba308"
        },
        {
            "question": "Football .................................... all over the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is playing",
                "is played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "890c69f57a224643a98ac9bb795272ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "The national anthem .................................... by the boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was singing",
                "was being sung"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "009c66b19ab54dfc8ee86a07b097689d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The match will certainly ....................................... by our team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "be won"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9f15ad9acc34ee68fb5dc8ad6c2d3c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The news ............................................... yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hasn't announced",
                "hasn't been announced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0f074fbd309b499e8d4202bd6291ad49"
        },
        {
            "question": "The answers are to ..................................... on both sides of the paper.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "be written",
                "be writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa2386cbde564fb78bdbfe922390787b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has always ..................................... by his supporters.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "admired",
                "been admired",
                "been admiring"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07ab675647a6469abe21d97516382de4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The roof is ....................................... by the contractor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fixing",
                "being fixing",
                "being fixed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cc28e635619a47079603b2ea23a74744"
        }
    ]
}